howtosay.co.in 2017-11-08

# Privacy Policy and Terms of Service of - howtosay.co.in

At www.howtosay.co.in, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.howtosay.co.in and how it is used.

## Personal identification information

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, subscribe to the newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities. 

## Privacy Policy and Terms of Service

### Terms and Conditions of Use for this site

The trademarks, logos, and service marks displayed on this Website, howtosay.co.in are registered and unregistered trademarks of its affiliates and others. Nothing contained on this Website should be construed as granting, by implication, estoppel, or otherwise, any license or right to use any Trademark displayed on this Website without the written permission of or such third party that may own the trademark displayed on this Website. Your misuse of the Trademarks displayed on this Website, or any other content on this Website, except as provided herein, is strictly prohibited. 

The data provided on this Web site could contain technical inaccuracies and typographical errors and all efforts are made to make sure the accuracy of the information on this Web site is correct, however this does not guarantee that there may not be any errors. Liability for errors and omissions in the contents of this Web site is expressly disclaimed. No claims, promises or warranties, express or implied, are made about the accuracy, completeness or fitness for purpose of any material on this Web site and about the reliability and about the dependability of the access to this Web site. No liability of any description is accepted, including liability for negligence, for any direct, indirect, special or consequential damages or losses resulting from the use of or the inability to use this Web site. No liability or responsibility is accepted for any failure to keep the information or for keeping the information in these documents up-to-date. You should not rely on any material in this Web site to make any decision or take any action as the material in this Web site does not constitute advice. The content of this website may be modified without notice. 

Unless otherwise specified, the copyright in the contents of all of the documents on this Web site is owned by the owner(s) of the domains of the Web site and all rights are reserved. Title to copyright in the contents of all of the documents on this Web site will at all times remain with the copyright owner. Users are permitted to copy some material for their personal use as private individuals only. No part of the data is to be republished either on another Web site or in any other medium, print, electronic or otherwise, or for any commercial service, without the prior written permission of the copyright owner. If you require any further information on permitted use, then please use the contact form. 

These terms and conditions that govern your usage of any or all of the text files that make up the Web sites known as howtosay.co.in. Please read through the Terms. If you do not agree with the Terms, then do not use the Web site. If you do use the Web site, then your use indicates that you agree to be bound by the Terms. Changes may be made in these terms and conditions at any time and without notice. Users are bound by such revisions and should therefore visit this page periodically to review the current Terms and Conditions. 

## Non-personal identification information

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

## Web browser cookies

Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

## Third party websites

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website's own terms and policies.

## How we use collected information

HowToSay.co.in may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:

  * **To improve customer service**

Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.

  * **To personalize user experience**

We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.

  * **To improve our Site**

We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.

* **To send periodic emails**

We may use the email address to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

## Log Files

Like many other Web sites, www.howtosay.co.in makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

## How we protect your information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

## Sharing your personal information

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission.

## Changes to this privacy policy

HowToSay.co.in has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

## Your acceptance of these terms

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

## Contacting us

    If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or any other dealings with this site, please contact us at:
    **howtosay.co.in**
    <http://www.howtosay.co.in/>
    **[[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)**

_This document was last updated on Des 21, 2014_
